=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 1=
= الحلقة 1 =
(There's a world in the other end of the universe, where the realms of Demon,)
(هناك عالم في الطرف الآخر من الكون ، حيث عوالم الشيطان ،)
(Immortal and Mortal have clear borders.)
(الخالدة والمميتة لها حدود واضحة).
(Each realm goes in its own way with order. However,)
(كل عالم يسير بطريقته الخاصة مع النظام. ومع ذلك ،)
(Princess Li Mingzhu of Huasheng Empire of the Mortal Realm)
(الأميرة لي مينجزو من إمبراطورية هواشنغ في عالم الموتى)
(is in love secretly with the Demon Emperor and bears his child.)
(يقع في حب الإمبراطور الشيطاني سرا ويحمل طفله).
(This makes the three realms eager for action.)
(هذا يجعل العوالم الثلاثة حريصة على العمل.)
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Mingzhu.
مينجزو.
(Princess of Huasheng Empire, Li Mingzhu) I can't carry on.
(أميرة إمبراطورية هواشنغ ، لي مينجزو) لا أستطيع الاستمرار.
(Emperor of Huasheng Empire, Li Mingtang)
(إمبراطور إمبراطورية هواشنغ ، لي مينغتانغ)
No. I must have a look.
لا. يجب أن ألقي نظرة.
(Empress of Huasheng Empire, Mu Nianhua) Your Majesty.
(إمبراطورة إمبراطورية هواشنغ ، مو نيانهوا) جلالة الملك.
Mingzhu, I am here.
مينجزو ، أنا هنا.
I am here, Mingzhu.
أنا هنا يا مينجزو.
Mingzhu.
مينجزو.
Look at our child.
انظر إلى طفلنا.
Let's name him.
دعونا نسميه.
Let's call him...
لنتصل به ...
Wuyou.
Wuyou.
That's a good name.
هذا اسم جيد.
You used up your essence to help me give birth to Wuyou.
لقد استخدمت جوهرك لمساعدتي في ولادة Wuyou.
I'm afraid
أنا خائف
we're going to die.
سنموت.
I fear no death.
لا أخشى الموت.
What I'm afraid of
ما أخاف منه
is to be without you in the Netherworld.
هو أن تكون بدونك في العالم السفلي.
Now that we've betrayed God's will,
الآن بعد أن خاننا مشيئة الله ،
from now on
من الان فصاعدا
Wuyou can only rely on himself.
يمكنك الاعتماد على نفسه فقط.
(20 years later)
(بعد 20 عاما)
(Huasheng Empire)
(إمبراطورية هواشنغ)
How long has the person been sent in?
كم من الوقت تم إرسال الشخص؟
Her Majesty.
جلالتها.
About
حول
an hour.
ساعة.
It seems like this one is fine.
يبدو أن هذا واحد على ما يرام.
I've
لدي
finally completed the task His Majesty assigned.
وأخيراً أكمل المهمة التي كلفها جلالة الملك.
(One.)
(واحد.)
(Two.)
(اثنين.)
(Three.)
(ثلاثة.)
Your face! Monster! Help!
وجهك!  مسخ!  مساعدة!
Zhang San. Li Si.
تشانغ سان. لي سي.
Roger.
حاضر.
Don't come near.
لا تقترب.
This is the sixth one.
هذا هو السادس.
It seems the daughters of the officials
يبدو بنات المسؤولين
are too coward.
جبناء جدا.
Next time,
المرة التالية،
find some boorish folk girls.
تجد بعض الفتيات الفلكلوريات.
I'm tired.
أنا مجهد.
Guard the entrance of the courtyard.
حراسة مدخل الفناء.
Don't let random people in.
لا تدع الأشخاص العشوائيين يدخلون.
So that they don't be frightened again.
حتى لا يخافوا مرة أخرى.
Yes, Her Majesty.
نعم صاحبة الجلالة.
(Guard of Demon Emperor, Rong Yueying)
(حارس إمبراطور الشياطين ، رونغ يويينغ)
Young Master, should I...
السيد الشاب ، هل يجب علي ...
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
I want to see
أريد أن أرى
(Son of Demon Emperor, Li Wuyou) what kind of girl she can find me.
(ابن الإمبراطور الشيطاني ، لي وويو) أي نوع من الفتيات يمكنها أن تجدني.
We didn't have a wedding ritual,
لم يكن لدينا طقوس الزفاف ،
yet there's a red veil.
حتى الآن هناك حجاب أحمر.
So unnecessary.
لا داعي لذلك.
I think so too.
أظن ذلك أيضا.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪
This is not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I don't get it.
انا لم احصل عليها.
But I'm shocked.
لكني مصدومة.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Which brainless person started the rumors?
أي شخص بلا عقل بدأ الشائعات؟
Saying you're an ugly monster.
أقول أنك وحش قبيح.
But according to me,
لكن بالنسبة لي ،
you're a beauty.
انت جميلة.
How can you tell?
كيف تستطيع أن تقول ذلك؟
It's said that inner beauty is more important.
يقال أن الجمال الداخلي أكثر أهمية.
Although half of your face is covered,
على الرغم من تغطية نصف وجهك ،
even if your entire face is covered,
حتى لو كان وجهك مغطى بالكامل ،
you can't escape my piercing eyes.
لا يمكنك الهروب من عيني الثاقبة.
What about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
You...
أنت...
(You're afraid indeed.)
(أنت خائف حقًا.)
You can change color.
يمكنك تغيير اللون.
You're so cool.
أنت رائع جدا.
Can you change into other colors?
هل يمكنك التغيير إلى ألوان أخرى؟
For example,
فمثلا،
yellow,
الأصفر،
green,
لون أخضر،
or blue?
أو الأزرق؟
Aren't you afraid after seeing me?
ألا تخافين بعد رؤيتي؟
Why should I be afraid?
لماذا يجب أن أخاف؟
As the saying goes,
على رأي القول،
there are good and bad people,
هناك أناس طيبون وسيئون ،
there are good and bad demons.
هناك شياطين جيدة وسيئة.
You're a human...
انت انسان ...
You have two bloodlines.
لديك سلالتان.
According to the folk rule of like begets like,
وفقا للحكم الشعبي من مثل يولد مثل ،
other than your look,
بخلاف مظهرك ،
you should have other...
يجب أن يكون لديك ...
Do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أكون؟
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪